## **SKILLS**

- ReactJS
- Javascript
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS/SASS
- Bootstrap

- Webpack
- NodeJS
- MongoDB
- Python
- SQL
- Git

### **SUMMARY**

Developer who possesses over three years of experience in front-end development. Enthusiastic about new technologies and passionate to build new solutions to improve user experience. I have a thirst of learning which is making myself a self-taught and motivated person. I'm not afraid to learn because I like challenges and surpass myself.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Front-End Developer / DOTSCREEN - Boulogne-Billancourt, FRANCE

12/2017 - 07/2020

Developed medias applications on STBs and TVs.

- Created from scratch and maintained applications.
- Optimized them in relation to devices abilities.
- Embed media players.
- Implemented analytics for audience.
- Collaborated with customers to determine needs and work through user experience.
- Used to Agile and SCRUM methodologies.
- Worked mainly on Freebox, Orange STBs, LG, Samsung (Tizen), HbbTV platforms.
- Contributed to applications for France.TV, ARTE, STARZPLAY, Disney, MiTele and others projects like BeinSport Connect, Deezer totalplay, OCS.

Languages: Javascript, jQuery, Webpack, TypeScript, HTML/CSS,

#### Front-End Developer / Kameleoon - Paris, France

07/2017 - 09/2017

- Collaborated with consultants to embed variations of A/B Testing
- Ensured the smooth running of the simulated Kameleoon product for most popular browsers.
- Responsive design

Languages and tools: Javascript, HTML/CSS, Sass

# System and Network Administrator / My Little Paris - Paris, France

09/2015 - 12/2015

- Analyzed software, network, system issues and assisted users in their resolutions.
- Prepped and applied basic configurations for various network and system hardwares.
- Implemented scripts to optimize time (GoogleScript and AppleScript).
- Took part of a study on Growth Social Media.

## **EDUCATION**

SUP'Internet, École Des Métiers De L'internet - Paris Project Management And Web Development 07/2017

EPITECH - European Institute Of Technology - Paris Computer Science

07/2016

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certification Full Stack Developer - FreeCodeCamp

# **LANGUAGES**

- French (native)
- English (professional)
- German (intermediate)